<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Diehl Sillers</title>
    <link>https://diehlms.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Diehl Sillers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 17:40:56 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://diehlms.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Search</title>
      <link>https://diehlms.github.io/post/job-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 17:40:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://diehlms.github.io/post/job-search/</guid>
      <description>Well folks, the job search has begun in earnest over the past few weeks. After I got back from Canada in early August, I promised myself I&#39;d get back on the horse and hit the job sites. So far a few nibbles from geology recruiters, but I&#39;ve yet to hear back from anyone in the tech world.
I imagine it&#39;s tough to take chances on self-taught developers with such a huge pool of CS grads and Bootcamp grads running around, but developing has actually been a pretty rewarding experience regardless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://diehlms.github.io/post/sample-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 18:11:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://diehlms.github.io/post/sample-post/</guid>
      <description>Howdy. This is my personal blog. Obviously, there is not a surplus of content here, so come back later when I think of something to say if and when that happens. Otherwise, checkout my other projects or find my code on my Github link above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>education</title>
      <link>https://diehlms.github.io/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://diehlms.github.io/education/</guid>
      <description>George Washington University B.S Geology, GIS Minor | Graduated May, 2018
Field work in Iceland (University of Iceland) and West Virginia
Coursework: Soil Science Current Crustal Movements Geophysics Geography of Iceland Civil &amp;amp; Environmental Engineering Chemistry (I &amp;amp; II) Physical Geology Historical Geology Oceanography Mineralogy Marine Geology Cartography &amp;amp; GIS Techniques of Spatial Analysis Igneous &amp;amp; Metamorphic Petrology Remote Sensing Structural Geology Sedimentology &amp;amp; Stratigraphy GIS II Digital Image Processing Hydrogeology Geological Field Methods</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>experience</title>
      <link>https://diehlms.github.io/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://diehlms.github.io/experience/</guid>
      <description>Apple, inc. via Apex GIS Technician
Austin, Texas | February, 2019 - present
 Implemented multiple pilot projects focused on data integrity, quality assurance, and data validation. Responsible for digitizing and assembling new content from various sources, including databases, files/spreadsheets, and client resources.   National Park Service Resource Management Assistant
Southeast Arizona | June, 2018 - December, 2018
 Implemented the pilot Unstable Slope Management Program (USMP) to document over 300 risky roadside and trailside geologic hazards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>projects</title>
      <link>https://diehlms.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://diehlms.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Iron City Fishing Club  Link Source Code Features: cabin reservation system, events calendar, blog, photo sharing system Technologies: Ruby/Ruby on Rails, postgres, leaflet.js, bootstrap, AWS S3 Status: development, live November 2019  NODRA  Link Source Code Features: results, contact list, blog, photo sharing system Technologies: Ruby/Ruby on Rails, postgres, bootstrap, AWS S3 Status: production  Nathaniel Wolfe  Link Source Code Features: music blog, geology blog Technologies: Ruby/Ruby on Rails, postgres, bootstrap Status: production</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>