<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-09-26T08:45:07-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Diehl Silers</title><subtitle>Diehl&apos;s musings</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Tubzich</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/stories/2025/09/25/tubzich.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tubzich" /><published>2025-09-25T05:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2025-09-25T05:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/stories/2025/09/25/tubzich</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/stories/2025/09/25/tubzich.html"><![CDATA[<p>“…”
“I suppose so. Not everyone here notices the way the skies dim and brighten, but it can’t be unexpected. When our brave explorer came back from your home with visual diaramas, we were amazed you could sit in awe for an evening at how your star falls down in front of you. Things dont work the same way here. Image is a paradox, you must not get used to the state of things as they are now. Expectation of one thing being in a place is a recipe for dissapointment. Expectation of a hue will be overruled the second you avert your attention
I will reiterate that everything is in motion. No object retains its shape for too long, including and especially us. I imagine it would be hard to get used to if you ever came and visited. Our light comes from the same star as it does you, but the clouds of gas and chemicals above us swirl and morph in fantastic ways”
“…”
“I know, I know. But your clouds have patterns. It may not seem like it, I know that when you look above your home or above the trees the white spots seem random and perplexing if you take the time to even notice them. The edges sometimes burn from the singe of the star rays shoving their way around them, or darken before a storm. They must look so immeasurable as to restrict any reason to really map them out. But I promise there is an order”
“But the mystery of your clouds is amplified here. The second you look the way of a stratotower your eyes may deceive yourself in believing in its existence - It simply flies away to another corner. That means the light throughout our days turns out not to mean much. Darkness comes and goes, your vision illuminates with no warning. Just as you begin to heat, you cool; sometimes you will feel sensations pushing you from multiple directions. It is just the natural order of things here.”
“…”
“Well we certainly still feel. I would guess our feelings aren’t too different than yours. Yes, when you are cold you might be cold eternally. And if hot, so on. When our skin dries up, our teeth chatter, we shiver, we feel cold just as you would if you were here. When the light hits us, even slightly, we warm up. It is just that there is at once no and limitless expectations. So yes, to point not too fine of a point on it, we get hot and cold”
“My family and I take walks every daycycle…”
“…”
“Sure, we have families. We can talk aobout that later. But as I was saying, we take walks on some regular cadence. We’re normal though, it is important to keep moving since not moving means ceding your movement to the land beneath you. We try to stay together but if we enter our own journeys we make sure to at least congregate at some known point later. Here, it might be confusing to you if I say a ‘known point’. That is, points surely are known but they do not appear as they were when you ‘know’ of them”
“…”
“I think I’m confusing you. But it is also hard to explain. When I was a small one, I would also walk with my family and elders out near wh</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="stories" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[“…” “I suppose so. Not everyone here notices the way the skies dim and brighten, but it can’t be unexpected. When our brave explorer came back from your home with visual diaramas, we were amazed you could sit in awe for an evening at how your star falls down in front of you. Things dont work the same way here. Image is a paradox, you must not get used to the state of things as they are now. Expectation of one thing being in a place is a recipe for dissapointment. Expectation of a hue will be overruled the second you avert your attention I will reiterate that everything is in motion. No object retains its shape for too long, including and especially us. I imagine it would be hard to get used to if you ever came and visited. Our light comes from the same star as it does you, but the clouds of gas and chemicals above us swirl and morph in fantastic ways” “…” “I know, I know. But your clouds have patterns. It may not seem like it, I know that when you look above your home or above the trees the white spots seem random and perplexing if you take the time to even notice them. The edges sometimes burn from the singe of the star rays shoving their way around them, or darken before a storm. They must look so immeasurable as to restrict any reason to really map them out. But I promise there is an order” “But the mystery of your clouds is amplified here. The second you look the way of a stratotower your eyes may deceive yourself in believing in its existence - It simply flies away to another corner. That means the light throughout our days turns out not to mean much. Darkness comes and goes, your vision illuminates with no warning. Just as you begin to heat, you cool; sometimes you will feel sensations pushing you from multiple directions. It is just the natural order of things here.” “…” “Well we certainly still feel. I would guess our feelings aren’t too different than yours. Yes, when you are cold you might be cold eternally. And if hot, so on. When our skin dries up, our teeth chatter, we shiver, we feel cold just as you would if you were here. When the light hits us, even slightly, we warm up. It is just that there is at once no and limitless expectations. So yes, to point not too fine of a point on it, we get hot and cold” “My family and I take walks every daycycle…” “…” “Sure, we have families. We can talk aobout that later. But as I was saying, we take walks on some regular cadence. We’re normal though, it is important to keep moving since not moving means ceding your movement to the land beneath you. We try to stay together but if we enter our own journeys we make sure to at least congregate at some known point later. Here, it might be confusing to you if I say a ‘known point’. That is, points surely are known but they do not appear as they were when you ‘know’ of them” “…” “I think I’m confusing you. But it is also hard to explain. When I was a small one, I would also walk with my family and elders out near wh]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog,/pinned/2025/09/25/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome" /><published>2025-09-25T05:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2025-09-25T05:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog,/pinned/2025/09/25/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog,/pinned/2025/09/25/welcome-to-jekyll.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="welcome">Welcome</h1>

<p>Since it’s 2025 and AI is coming for all content hosted online, not to mention all our jobs, figured I better get a blog out there!</p>

<p><br /></p>

<h2 id="dreams">Dreams</h2>

<p>These are just the dreams that I remember for long enough in the morning to jot down in my notepad.</p>

<p>Expect there to be significant gaps between them.</p>

<p>All references to real people are entirely circumstantial.</p>

<p><br /></p>

<h2 id="short-stories-to-come">Short stories to come</h2>

<p>…<br /></p>

<h2 id="technical-guides-to-come">Technical guides to come</h2>

<p>…</p>

<p><br />
<br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog," /><category term="pinned" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sisters</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/dreams/2024/01/13/sisters.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sisters" /><published>2024-01-13T12:46:53-08:00</published><updated>2024-01-13T12:46:53-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/dreams/2024/01/13/sisters</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/dreams/2024/01/13/sisters.html"><![CDATA[<p>I guess this one has a build up that I don’t remember. As far as I can recall, I was on a quest to find out where my sisters were and if confronted with their captor, enact my vengance. Hard to imagine myself enacting vengance in real life, but oh well.</p>

<p>I pulled my car into a grove, passing a lot of beat up cars parked alongside a brook, maybe 20 in total. Oak trees were outstretched over the road, shading most of the property. It was quite beautiful, aside from the junk cars, if you could gaze at the main house which resided along a river. The day was muggy and slightly cloudy.</p>

<p>The property owner came out to see who pulled in. He asked quite suspiciously who I was. If I told him, I quickly asked him if he knew where my sisters were. Unclear to me how or why I thought he knew where they would be, I probed and accused more forcefully until he relented. He pointed me to a shack behind the main house and asked me to follow him. Wordlessly he led me to a small footbridge wide enough for only one person at a time. I went first, reaching the other side and sensing his raised fist behind me.</p>

<p>I turned around and caught him migrating his stance from one of threat to a wide outstretched yawn. Clever tactic I suppose. He unlocked the shed. Nothing. I became berzerk, I started throwing fists and we started going at it, dragging each other to the floor. Blow after blow for minutes, until we drain our energies. No upper hand.</p>

<p>“What did you hit me for”, he asked pantingly. “You know where they are” I answereed with all the courage and accusatory force I could find in my psyche between gasps for air.</p>

<p>“I dont even know who you are”</p>

<p>“…”</p>

<p>“Everyone’s a liar”</p>

<p>Hard to know what to make of this one.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="dreams" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I guess this one has a build up that I don’t remember. As far as I can recall, I was on a quest to find out where my sisters were and if confronted with their captor, enact my vengance. Hard to imagine myself enacting vengance in real life, but oh well.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rhino</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/dreams/2024/01/13/rhino.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rhino" /><published>2024-01-13T12:46:39-08:00</published><updated>2024-01-13T12:46:39-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/dreams/2024/01/13/rhino</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/dreams/2024/01/13/rhino.html"><![CDATA[<p>A bit more of a nightmare. It was nighttime and I was hanging with some a handful of others outside the back of the kitchen in Iron City. I had a club or weapon of some kind in my hand and was sort of pacing. I wasn’t nervous, but the mood had a celebatory flavor so it was hard to settle. People were milling about, laughing and goofing off. I looked around and noticed most people, still only a handful at this time, had similar handheld weapons.</p>

<p>Suddenly I got nervous with an impending sense of doom. Something was about to go horribly wrong. The other people around me were beginning to queue up and I shuffled my way in line. After a minute I removed myself and started towards the back, walking around the front of the dining hall until I saw more and more people streaming in from the beach and front lawn, all equiped with makeshift bats, clubs, instruments of damage.</p>

<p>I was almost near the rear of the line before I find the silhouette of the Rhino cast onto the white plaster wall. A cheer rippled through the line and the crowds mood ascended into restless excitment as quickly as mine sank to dread. The rhino was picking people from the line one by one and mauling them into shreds. It didn’t seem to damper the jubliation at all. The clubs were there for the group assault on the rhino but the odds were always stacked against us. Others with grins on their face continued to laugh and play until it was their turn with the beast.</p>

<p>I left the crowd behind and walked along the boardwalk, then hopped off to meander around the rocky shore. A native man I didnt recongnize was smoking on a precipice as the water lapped at his feet. I approached and began making conversation; he wondered why I wasnt with the others. We could still hear them across the water; the night was still and the bay carries sound as if there is no distance.</p>

<p>I said I felt uncomfortable, I guess I wasnt ready to die. He remarked about the ignorance of our clan. I dont know if he was grouping me in with them as well, but I don’t know why he’d exclude me.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="dreams" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bit more of a nightmare. It was nighttime and I was hanging with some a handful of others outside the back of the kitchen in Iron City. I had a club or weapon of some kind in my hand and was sort of pacing. I wasn’t nervous, but the mood had a celebatory flavor so it was hard to settle. People were milling about, laughing and goofing off. I looked around and noticed most people, still only a handful at this time, had similar handheld weapons.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Circus</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/dreams/2023/12/21/circus.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Circus" /><published>2023-12-21T06:20:47-08:00</published><updated>2023-12-21T06:20:47-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/dreams/2023/12/21/circus</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/dreams/2023/12/21/circus.html"><![CDATA[<ul>
  <li>two stage play</li>
  <li>houdini esque</li>
  <li>big platform on rope</li>
  <li>big water tank</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="dreams" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[two stage play houdini esque big platform on rope big water tank]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Car Crash</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/dreams/2023/12/18/car-crash.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Car Crash" /><published>2023-12-18T09:41:12-08:00</published><updated>2023-12-18T09:41:12-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/dreams/2023/12/18/car-crash</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/dreams/2023/12/18/car-crash.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="car-crash">Car Crash</h1>

<p>Went for a drive through a residential neighborhood. Was with some other people, dont know who though. The car was silent while we turned and saw the aftermath of a quite violent collision of another car. We saw chunks of what was once a truck as well as debris of loose tree limbs and various trash and refuse across the streets. We turned on to a boulevard, so the car was on the otherside of a shaded skinny median. I hopped out of the car without speaking. The car i was driving in must have been stopped.</p>

<p>I ran across the street and saw the man who was driving the crumbled mush of a truck sitting on the curb, not looking deathly but not in the best of spirits which didnt surprise me. I didnt interact with him at all, just waltzed past after scanning the scene and took out my phone. It was getting dark so I began flashing my phone flashlight at other cars coming down the road. Some of them registered the blinking flash light of at least something that should be paid attention to; less cars heeded the warning that I guess I was trying to convey.</p>

<p>I went for a walk, and eventually met a chain link fenced which blocked in a playing field that some kids were using for soccer. I walked through the fence gate diagonally through the field trying not to seem suspicious but also not advertising that I wanted to play. I likely did want to play but was never going to approach these tweens about coming on for a quick match. I was in some business casual outfit, with seamless shoes not ergonomic for kicking. Nevertheless the players shanked the ball over to my direction as I passed by. Trying to be cheeky I attempted to flick the ball up with the toe portion of my business shoes, severely miscalculating the attempted angle of ascent, sending the ball above my shoulders at an awkward obtuse angle. Never saw the ball actually come back down.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="dreams" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Car Crash]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Austin</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/dreams/2023/12/17/austin.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Austin" /><published>2023-12-17T12:52:50-08:00</published><updated>2023-12-17T12:52:50-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/dreams/2023/12/17/austin</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/dreams/2023/12/17/austin.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="austin">Austin</h1>

<p>Whatever was of Austin is no longer. The streets inexplicably are void of asphalt, reverted back to their gravel origins or overgrown with brush. No houses had AC, though all the buildings were still there. The air was tinged with a brown orange usually seen around late summer when all the grass has burned away reflecting the brown of the soil back to the sky; a normal early September.</p>

<p>There was a person that mentioned everyone went down to San Antonio. Didn’t sound like anything catastrophic happened, apparently it happened naturally and not so fast that San Antonio burst at the seams with all the new residents. I guess there were still a few stragglers in Austin, this man included. I don’t remember seeing anyone though, it was really quiet.</p>

<p>I woke up and saw there was a shooting on 6th street. I guess someone brought a gun into a bar and the cops killed him, with a few shots in the chaos finding other patrons. I googled the story and accidentally clicked on the article about the other shooting.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="dreams" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Austin]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Art School</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/dreams/2023/12/12/art-school.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Art School" /><published>2023-12-12T08:19:57-08:00</published><updated>2023-12-12T08:19:57-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/dreams/2023/12/12/art-school</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/dreams/2023/12/12/art-school.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="art-school">Art School</h1>

<p>The class and I sat in arrays of rectangular black-top rolling tables. About thirty people in total. We all went up, one by one, to demo our paintings to the class. We would bring up our canvases up to the easel in the front, and reveal the same painting subject to the audience. The subject was some kind of queen, in royal regalia. Most of us used the same techniques, and similar color palatte. Red velvety robe type garmint, pointy crown, big thone.</p>

<p>I went up and displayed my work. I dont remember talking about my piece. I thought it was okay. Nothing groundbreaking, but not bad. The painting was definitely a queen, or at least could easily be mistaken for one; if you told a stranger the person in the painting was a queen, the stranger would probably accept that. Some sloppy handiwork, some odd bright spots here and there. My classmates seemed to like it, but maybe that’s an egoist hindsight.</p>

<p>The next artist went up. Her piece was amazing. It was inspiring and took the queen subject in a completely novel direction. I couldnt believe what I was seeing, nor believe how moved I was by it. The colors were alive and warm. The queen wasnt wearing clothes like in all the other paintings. There were scars, I definitely remember; big fleshy streaks across the back that looked raw and painful. The person was looking over their shoulder, seemingly through the viewer. No one in the audience seemed to have much of a reaction. Maybe I didn’t either, since I dont remember talking or making any kind of noise or fidget.</p>

<p>I was in a car with two others, driving fast down a highway displaying the symptoms of a road beginning to clog. Lots of jerking brakes and lurching forward from the heavy foot of the driver. I wasnt driving, and I think i was in the back seat. The other passenger began convulsing shortly after coming out from under an overpass, sputtering saliva over the plexiglass. It took a minute for the driver to pay attention although neither one of us seemed to behave with what was probably the required urgency. We pulled over on the road and parked as if we simply making a quick pit stop at the grocery. The driver grabbed the woman having the heart attack and layed her on the road. Beginning CPR, he heaved and thrashed against her chest no doubt breaking ribs. We took turns but I doubt I was giving her the needed effort to revive her failing heart. I don’t remember if she made it.</p>

<p>I was walking into the university student center and administration building. There was the odd mix of faculty and administration in suits walking between foosball and ping pong tables. The hallway I was in was bright with a sharp light blue hue coming through tiled glass bricks. A vendor was standing right inside the entrance. I offered her an egg from my satchel but she politely declined. She pointed up the hallway and said he might like one.</p>

<p>She was pointing to a friend from college that I think was walking his girlfriend on a leash. I offered him an egg and he graciously accepted. Sorry to say i dont think i offered his girlfriend an egg, though I had plenty to share.</p>

<p>At the same university, at the same student center I continued to walk through the hall until it opened up into the main foyer. The room expanded conically into a wide ampitheature with tall stadium seating. I had entered at the tip of the cone into the top row of seating. Everyone was glued to the tv monitors scattered along the walls and dangling from the roof. Nearly everyone had baseball jerseys, though we were in Germany. As dreams go it didnt make much sense.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="dreams" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art School]]></summary></entry></feed>